aviationcv.com 2019-04-04

# Aviation Jobs and Aviation Employment - AviationCV.com

**AVIATIONCV.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

Your privacy is the most important objective to AviationCV.com. This privacy policy describes the ways we collect, store, use, transfer your personal information and protect it. You accept this Policy by signing up for or using our services or any other features offered by us on our website or through any other means (collectively the “AviationCV.com Services").

We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it.

1\. Collection and use of personal information

1.1. Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person.

1.2. You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with AviationCV.com or its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, employees, agents, partners and licensors. AviationCV.com and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, employees, agents, partners and licensors may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.

1.3. What personal information we collect. When you create an AviationCV.com account or use any other services provided by AviationCV.com, we may collect a variety of information, including:

1.3.1. Name, surname/Company name;

1.3.2. Mailing address, residence, e-mail address;

1.3.3. Phone/fax number;

1.3.4. Credit card information;

1.3.5. Consumer and market research data:

1.3.5.1. Account type;

1.3.5.2. Account password;

1.3.5.3. Any other related information.

1.4. How we use your personal information. We use the information we collect in order to:

1.4.1. Create and manage your account;

1.4.2. Manage our sites and services;

1.4.3. Assist you in the processing of your requirements;

1.4.4. Send information, and advertisement (with the prior consent from you);

1.4.5. Improve offers, products, services and advertising content;

1.4.6. Offer other products and services;

1.4.7. Develop and deliver products, services you request;

1.4.8. Develop new products and services;

1.4.9. Process payment for purchasers or other services;

1.4.10. Protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions;

1.4.11. Analyze trends, analyze the use of our products, services, and sites;

1.4.12. Determine the effectiveness of our advertising;

1.4.13. Enforce our Terms and Conditions and otherwise manage our business;

1.4.14. Fulfill legal and regulatory requirements.

1.5. All the information we collect about you may be combined to help us tailor our communications to you and to develop world-class products and services.

1.6. Information sharing and disclosure to third-parties. AviationCV.com and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, employees, agents, partners and licensors may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. AviationCV.com does not disclose any non-public personal information about you to any other entities, except as referred to the Privacy policy or required/permitted by law. AviationCV.com also may share personal information with entities who provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These entities are obligated to protect your information as settled in AviationCV.com Privacy policy.

 1.7. We also may share your information:

1.7.1. With our third-party service suppliers, including those who work on behalf of AviationCV.com and our business partners to send you joint communications that can be interesting to you;

1.7.2. If AviationCV.com brand is sold to another company;

1.7.3. For the protection of AviationCV.com property.

2\. Cookies, web beacons and other technologies

2.1 Definitions:

2.1.1. A cookie, also known as a web cookie, browser cookie, and HTTP cookie, is a piece of text stored by a user's web browser. A cookie can be used for authentication, storing site preferences, shopping cart contents, the identifier for a server-based session, or anything else that can be accomplished through storing text data.

2.1.2.Web beacons are small bits of code embedded in web pages or in emails.

 2.2. Purpose of cookies and other technologies. We use these technologies to provide you a richer and more personalized consumer experience. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, facilitate and measure the effectiveness of our services, advertisements and web searches, analyze trends and improve the quality of the webpage.

We also allow third-parties to display advertising on our websites. In order to recognize your computer, some of these companies may place a cookie on your computer when sending you an online advertisement. This enables them to understand the place, where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisement and deliver ads that they believe are of interest to you. AviationCV.com does not control these third companies’ use of cookies.

**Cookies** | **The purpose of data managment** | **Necessity** | **The moment of creation** | **The period of validity** | **The data used** | **Additional Information**  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
cb-enabled |   |   |   |   |   | This cookie is associated with a free script which shows a cookie alert notice on a website. It is used to record when the user has dismissed the notice to prevent it re-appearing on return visits.  
_cfduid |   |   |   |   |   | Is used to override any security restrictions based on the IP address the visitor is coming from  
Tawk_* |   |   |   |   |   | Messaging app that lets you monitor and chat with visitors on our website  
TawkConnectionTime  
_tawkuuid  
_ym_visorc_32116576 | yandex metrics cookie <td rowspan="3" ,="">  |  | 

Until the browser window is closed.

| Protects character “w”, it is not personal information. | Yandex Metrica - Cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use the Site.  
_ym_uid  
_ym_isad  
_gat |   | Tracking Cookies. Optional, without these Cookies system would work. However, these Cookies are recommended. | Entering the site | 2 years | Used to throttle request rate. | Google Analytics - Cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use the Site. This uses the system developed by Google that is used on the majority of websites.   
_ga |   | Distinguishes Users.  
bt2 |   |   |   | 2 years |   | Third party cookie used to access functions like print,email,facebook,twitter and SHARING.  
loc  
ssc  
di2  
uvc  
uid  
um  
vc  
_atuvc  
_atuvs  
lang |   |   |   |   |   | To determine language of the website  
  
3\. Protection of personal information.

AviationCV.com takes all necessary administrative, technical and physical precautions to protect your personal information against loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

3.1. AviationCV.com recommends you to use an SSL-enabled browser (Safari, Firefox, Internet Explorer, etc.) when ordering our services.

3.2. AviationCV.com limits the access to personal information to those who have a business need.     Personal information is kept only for a reasonable amount of time and useless information is destroyed.

4\. Children Privacy policy.

AviationCV.com does not intend to collect personal information of children under 14. We kindly encourage parents and guardians to monitor children online activity.

5\. Governing law.

All disputes and any claim related directly or indirectly to this Privacy policy shall be governed and construed under the laws of the Republic of Lithuania. The court of the Republic of Lithuania at the registration place of AviationCV.com shall have exclusive jurisdiction to settle any unsolved disputes which may arise out, under, or in connection with this Privacy policy and the use of our website.

6\. Privacy questions.

If you have any questions or concerns related to AviationCV.com Privacy policy, please contact us.
